Stanislaw M. Ulam Papers 1916-1984 Mss.Ms.Coll.54
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Professional correspondence, 1932-1986, 15.5 Linear feet 33 boxes
  - Wiesner, Jerome B., 1961-1971; n.d. (Box Series I-30)
    ROVER & ORION
    See Hill, Albert G.
  - Wiggin, Blanton C., 1983 (Box Series I-30)
    Number series
  - Wigner, Eugene P., 1957-1978 (Box Series I-30)
    Reactor symp.
  - Wilcox, Ralph M., 1970 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wild, John M., 1964 (Box Series I-30)
    ORION
  - Wilder, R. L., 1967 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wiley, Norbet, 1981 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wiley-Interscience, 1970-1978 (Box Series I-30)
  - Williams, John D., 1949-1957 (Box Series I-30)
    RAND;JVN
  - Williams, Larry, 1966 (Box Series I-30)
    SMU's set theory course
  - Williams, Lloyd B., 1958-1959 (Box Series I-30)
  - Williams, Stan, 1982 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wilson, E. Bright, 1949 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wilson, J. S., 1969 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wilson, Paul A., 1958 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wilson, R. Lynn, 1972-1973 (Box Series I-30)
    LASL consultant agreements
  - Wing, G. Milton, 1973-1978 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wing, Nina (Mrs. G. Milton), 1969 (Box Series I-30)
  - Winstead, Warren J., 1966-1967 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wirszup, Izaak, 1980 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wirth, Tim, 1979 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wishart, Arthur W., 1966-1968;n.d. (Box Series I-30)
  - Wisner, Bob, 1972 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wisniewski, W. L., 1957 (Box Series I-30)
  - Witten, Edward, 1981 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wlodarski, J., 1971 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wohlberg, Margaret, 1975 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wojcik, Richard R., 1975 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wolf, Katie R., 1944 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wolf, Robert A., 1961 (Box Series I-30)
    General Atomic; ORION
  - Wolfe, Hugh C., 1961 (Box Series I-30)
    SANE; Test Ban Treaty
  - Wolfe, Philip, 1955 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wolfram, Stephen (Box Series I-30)
    See Farmer, Doyne
  - Wolkowisky, Jay, 1970-1974 (Box Series I-30)
  - Worlton, Jack, 1977 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wright, Fred B., 1976 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wrubel, Marshal H., 1962 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wszelaki, Jan, 1964 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wunderlich, M. C. (Box Series I-30)
    - Folder #1, 1962-1969 (Box Series I-30)
    - Folder #2, n.d. (Box Series I-30)
      Hilbert's 10th problem
  - Wyden, Peter, 1983 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wydro, Jan, 1983 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wyman, Jeffries, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wynne, Allen, 1976 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wysocki, Theodore, 1969 (Box Series I-30)
  - Wyss, Walter, 1981 (Box Series I-30)
  - Yamasaki, Shin'inchiro, 1952 (Box Series I-31)
  - Yang, C. T., 1954 (Box Series I-31)
  - Yang, Eileen, 1980 (Box Series I-31)
  - Yankelevich, E., 1981 (Box Series I-31)
  - Yanoff, Michael, 1980 (Box Series I-31)
  - Yarbrough, Edward, 1980 (Box Series I-31)
    Spirals, primes
  - Yevick, Miriam L., 1971 (Box Series I-31)
  - York, Herbert F., 1958-1976 (Box Series I-31)
    Nuclear history
  - Young, David M., 1959; 1961 (Box Series I-31)
  - Young, John V., 1963 (Box Series I-31)
    re: H-bomb invention
    Shearer, Lloyd
  - Youngs, J. W. T., 1950 (Box Series I-31)
  - Yourgrau, Wolfgang, 1967-1968 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zabusky, Charlotte, 1975 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zabusky, Norman (Box Series I-31)
    - Folder #1, 1959-1965 (Box Series I-31)
      International School of Nonlinear Mathematics and Physics
    - Folder #2, 1966-1970 (Box Series I-31)
    - Folder #3, 1971-1980 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zacharias, Jerrold R., 1966-1967; 1982 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zadina, Edward J., 1973 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zadworski, Zenon, 1974 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zaharia, S. D., 1981 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zaks, Joseph, 1971 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zaleski, Stephane, 1982-1983 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zawacki, Edmund, 1964; 1978; 1980 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zawadzka, Regina J., 1938 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zelen, Marvin, 1983 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zener, C., 1961 (Box Series I-31)
  - Ziemba, Walter J., 1971 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zietlow, Paul, 1982 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zinman, Walter G., 1971; 1977 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zinn, John, 1967 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zippin, Leo, 1959 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zolzistaw[?], A[lex], n.d. (Box Series I-31)
  - Zotcinski, Edward, 1977 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zuckerkandl, Emile, 1979 (Box Series I-31)
  - Zygmund, Antoni, 1940-1983 (Box Series I-31)
    Some in Polish; 7/11/45 letter re: deaths during WWII
    See Engelking, Ryszard
- Series II. Personal correspondence, 1936-1979, 0.5 Linear feet 1 box
  Letters, postcards, and telegrams to Ulam from various family members and friends from Poland and the United States. Manuscripts are arranged alphabetically by correspondent's name and chronologically within each file. The bulk of the material dates from 1936 to the beginning of World War II, while Ulam was teaching at Harvard University. A significant portion of this series is in Polish, and the subjects have not been determined.
  The collective family correspondence (2 folders) is potentially of some biographical interest. While in many cases the writers have not been identified, it appears that Ulam's father, Jozef, is a regular participant in these group letters as they most often appear on his Lwów law office letterhead. Perhaps the most poignant English-language letter from Series II is one written by a cousin, Juliusz (Julek) Ulam, in March 16, 1945, informing Ulam that his immediate family, including father, sister, brother-in-law, and uncle "all fell from the hands of the Nazis." One of the most vivid features of the personal correspondence is surely the depiction of life in Poland before the outbreak of World War II.
  - Auerbach, Jozef, 1939 (Box Series II-1)
  - Auerbach, Klara, 1938 (Box Series II-1)
    Aunt
    See Auerbach, Mike
  - Auerbach, Mike, 1938 (Box Series II-1)
    Cousin; note from Klara Auerbach in Polish; poem
  - Brenner, Maksymiljan, 1938 (Box Series II-1)
  - Brett, Lily, 1947 (Box Series II-1)
  - Bussgang, Julian J., 1949-1955 (Box Series II-1)
  - Collective Family Correspondence (Box Series II-1)
    - Folder #1, 1936-1937 (Box Series II-1)
      In Polish; several family
    - Folder #2, 1938-1949; n.d. (Box Series II-1)
      Correspondents on each letter
  - Diamant, L., 1940 (Box Series II-1)
  - Goldberg, Izydor, 1947 (Box Series II-1)
    Uncle
  - Goldberg, Lusia, 1946-1959; n.d. (Box Series II-1)
    Aunt; Some in Polish
  - Gruss, Jozef, 1940; n.d. (Box Series II-1)
  - Hofstadter, Douglas R., 1977 (Box Series II-1)
    Photocopy of Polish address book mentioning relatives
  - Menkes, Zygmund, 1936-1979; n.d. (Box Series II-1)
    Mainly in Polish
  - Plesch, Leonie, 1947 (Box Series II-1)
  - Richet, Tosia, n.d. (Box Series II-1)
  - Thon, Jerry, 1939 (Box Series II-1)
  - Ulam, Adam (Box Series II-1)
    Brother; Some in Polish
    - Folder #1, 1939-1977 (Box Series II-1)
    - Folders #2-3, n.d. (Box Series II-1)
  - Ulam, Alex[ander] (Box Series II-1)
    -See Ser. I, Ballen, Samuel B.
  - Ulam, Andrezj, 1936-1948;n.d. (Box Series II-1)
  - Ulam, Françoise, 1944; 1973; 1984; 1986 (Box Series II-1)
    -See also Ser. I, Budrewicz, [?]
    -See also Ser. I, Gardner, Martin
    -See also Ser. I, von Neumann, John
  - Ulam, Jozef, 1936-1938 (Box Series II-1)
    Father; in Polish
  - Ulam, Juliusz (Julek) (Box Series II-1)
    Cousin; Some in Polish
    - Folder #1, 1939-1949 (Box Series II-1)
      16.III.45 gives news that immediate family killed by Nazis during WWII
    - Folder #2, 1953-1979 (Box Series II-1)
  - Ulam, Marysia, 1936-1937 (Box Series II-1)
  - Ulam, Szymon, 1936-1948 (Box Series II-1)
  - Unknown (Box Series II-1)
    - Folder #1, 1936-1940 (Box Series II-1)
    - Folder #2, 1940-1949; n.d. (Box Series II-1)
- Series III. Polish materials, 1935-1984, 0.53 Linear feet 1 box
  Untranslated correspondence, early mathematical notes, and miscellaneous Polish newspaper articles dating from Ulam's first months at the Institute for Advanced Study in Princeton through the end of his life. Series III houses a significant portion of the Polish correspondence found throughout the collection, except for Polish letters with identified correspondents. These can be found in the alphabetical arrangement of Series I and II. Mathematical notes in this series include some of Ulam's early studies in mathematics, before he began working primarily in English. These original research documents are the most noteworthy aspects of this series. There are also a few notes in the hand of unidentified Polish colleagues. All notes of Series III remain undated, as do most of the Polish newspaper clippings.
  - Correspondence (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #1, 1935-1939 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #2, 1940-1949 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #3, 1950-1964 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #4, 1965-1971 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #5, 1972-1975 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #6, 1976-1977 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #7, 1978-1979 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #8, 1980-1981 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #9, 1982-1983 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #10, 1984 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #11, n.d. (Box Series III-1)
  - Mathematical Notes (Box Series III-1)
    - 2 Folders, n.d. (Box Series III-1)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1981; n.d. (Box Series III-1)
- Series IV. Subject files, ca.1945-1983, 1.5 Linear feet 3 boxes
  Diverse materials dating from Ulam's initial involvements at LASL through his final years of life, arranged alphabetically by topic. While many of the files hold correspondence relating to specific subjects of interest to Ulam, there are various other materials, such as information booklets, scientific symposium agendas, proposals, and miscellaneous documents. Many of the files reflect Ulam's participation in learned and professional societies and events in the scientific community. Some of the larger subject files contain Ulam's invitations to lecture at universities and societies, National Science Foundation proposals submitted to Ulam for review, and letters of recommendation for graduate students. Among the files of particular interest are several containing information on LASL. This is noted on the container listing.
  - [Administration of graduate students], 1960-1968;n.d. (Box Series IV-1)
  - Air Force Space Study Committee, 1960-1961 (Box Series IV-1)
    Projects ORION and ROVER
  - American Mathematical Society, 1946-1958 (Box Series IV-1)
    misc.
  - American Mathematical Society., 1957-1958 (Box Series IV-1)
    Gibbs lecture committee
  - American Mathematical Society., 1956-1960 (Box Series IV-1)
    Correspondence
    Mathematical Reviews
  - American Mathematical Society., 1959-1961;n.d. (Box Series IV-1)
    Mathematical Surveys Editorial Committee
  - American Mathematical Society., 1960-1961 (Box Series IV-1)
    Symposium on Mathematical Problems in the Biological Sciences
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1 Jan. 1958 (Box Series IV-1)
    Diagram organization
  - Autobiographical information (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #1, 1980-1982;n.d. (Box Series IV-1)
      Vita
    - Folder #2, 1966-1978 (Box Series IV-1)
      Essays
    - Folder #3, 1984-1985;n.d. (Box Series IV-1)
      Publication lists
  - Crackpots (Box Series IV-1)
    Corresp. and papers
    - Folder #1, 1959 (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #2, 1959-1969 (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #3, 1970-1971 (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #4, 1971-1974; n.d. (Box Series IV-1)
  - Employment, contracts of, 1945-1971 (Box Series IV-1)
    Consultant agreements; LASL Project Y
  - Employment, offers of, 1936-1955 (Box Series IV-1)
  - Grusin, Claire Ulam, n.d. (Box Series IV-1)
  - H-Bomb Conference, Princeton, 21-23 June 1982 (Box Series IV-1)
    See also Series XV: Bundy, McGeorge and Smyth, H.D.
  - Harvard Symposium on Digital, 3-6 April 1961 (Box Series IV-1)
    Abstract: Computers and Their Applications
  - Hycon Manufacturing Company, 1960-1962 (Box Series IV-1)
    Patents
  - International Congress of Mathematicians, Warsaw Meeting, 11-19 Aug. 1982 (Box Series IV-1)
  - Invitations to give talks (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #1, 1956-1967 (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #2, 1968 (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #3, 1968 (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #4, 1969 (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #5, 1970 (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #6, 1970 (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #7, 1971-1972 (Box Series IV-1)
    - Folder #8, 1973 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #9, 1974; n.d. (Box Series IV-2)
  - Jurzykowki Foundation, Inc. (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #1, 1963-1974 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #2, 1975-1976 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #3, 1977-1978 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #4, 1979 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #5, 1980-1981 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #6, 1982-1983;n.d. (Box Series IV-2)
  - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory, 1946-1949;n.d. (Box Series IV-2)
    Misc. memos; diagrams of personnel organization
  - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory. Laboratory Policy Committee, 1960-1961 (Box Series IV-2)
    Minutes, outlines, summaries of research
  - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory. Unclassified reports (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #1, 1 Jan. 1958 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #2, 29 Jan. 1958 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #3, 12 Feb. 1958 (Box Series IV-2)
  - Mathematical Association of America. The American Mathematical Monthly, 1959-1960 (Box Series IV-2)
  - Mathematical Association of America. Visiting lecturer, 1959 (Box Series IV-2)
  - Mathematical Profiles Project (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #1, 1957 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #2, 1958 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #3, 1958 (Box Series IV-2)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #1, 1966-1967 (Box Series IV-2)
      minutes, by-laws, constitution
    - Folder #2, 1966-1982? (Box Series IV-2)
      nomination, program, biographical info.
  - National Academy of Sciences, election to, 1966 (Box Series IV-2)
    Congratulatory correpondence
    Abelson, Philip H.
    Baker, Bill
    Bing, R. H.
    Brauer, Richard
    Breit, Gregory
    Brickwidde, F. G.
    Courant, R.
    Dominick, Peter H.
    Floberg, John F.
    Gamow, Mr. and Mrs. Igor
    Goldhaber, Maurice and Trude
    Hornig, Donald F.
    Humphrey, Hubert H.
    Kerr, Clark
    Kerst, Donald W.
    Knous, Robert L.
    Kolodner, I. I.
    Kuchel, Thomas H.
    Love, John A.
    Neyman, Jerzy
    Puck, Ted
    Richtmyer, Jane
    Rinehart, R. F.
    Schmidt, Eric W.
    Seaborg, Glenn T.
    Steinhaus, Hugo
    Tarski, Alfred
    Taub, Abe
    Todd, John
    Tuve, Merle A.
    Waddington, C. H.
    Wallace, Alexander Doniphan
    Walsh, J. L.
    Wilder, R. L.
  - National Academy of Sciences. National Research Council, 1956-1959 (Box Series IV-2)
  - National Science Foundation Proposals (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #1, 1956 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #2, 1956 (Box Series IV-2)
    - Folder #3, 1956 (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #4, 1957-1958 (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #5, 1958 (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #6, 1959 (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #7, 1960-1961 (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #8, 1972-1973;n.d. (Box Series IV-3)
  - See also Series VIII: Bednarck, A. R. and S. M. Ulam (Box Series IV-3)
  - NOBSKA, Project, 1956 (Box Series IV-3)
  - Nuclear Reactor Theory, Symposium on, 1958-1959 (Box Series IV-3)
  - ORION project patent, 1960 (Box Series IV-3)
    British
  - Personnel questionnaires, [1950?]-1952 (Box Series IV-3)
    Johns Hopkins University
  - Press releases, War Department., [1945?] (Box Series IV-3)
    Atomic Bomb Project
  - Proposals, 1960 (Box Series IV-3)
    Misc.
  - Recommendations, letters of, 1947-1981 (Box Series IV-3)
    Graduate students
    - Folder #1 A-D (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #2 E-I (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #3 J-N (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #4 O-Z (Box Series IV-3)
  - Test Ban Treaty, 1963-1965;n.d. (Box Series IV-3)
    See also Series I: Anderson, Clinton P. and Mechem, E. L.
  - Vietnam, A Statement on U.S. Policy in, 1968 (Box Series IV-3)
  - Weizmann Institute of Science (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #1, 1960-1964 (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #2, 1965-1974 (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #3, 1975-1978 (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #4, 1979-1980 (Box Series IV-3)
    - Folder #5, 1981-1983 (Box Series IV-3)
- Series V. Research notes, 1934-1983, 2.0 Linear feet 4 boxes
  Ulam's original, unclassified research papers divided into two formats: notebooks and note pads (1934-1983) and unbound loose notes (1937-1983). Both groups are arranged chronologically, reflecting the major movements of Ulam's career from research notes made in Poland, through his positions at American universities and LASL. The notes relate to Ulam's personal research interests, rather than notes prepared for class lectures (which are housed separately in Series X). Forty notebooks and note pads as well as twenty-three folders of loose notes, graphs, and computer printouts on paper provide an overview of the research and mathematical problems that were the focus of Ulam's work throughout his lifetime. Much of the scientific and mathematical notation is unlabeled or undated.
  - Research notebook (Box Series V-1)
    - Folder #1, 1934 (Box Series V-1)
      Poland; in Polish
    - Folder #2, 1935 (Box Series V-1)
      Poland/Princeton? In Polish
    - Folder #3, 1936-1937 (Box Series V-1)
      Princeton/Harvard? In Polish
    - Folder #4, 1938 (Box Series V-1)
    - Folder #5, ca. 1939-1941 (Box Series V-1)
      University of Wisconsin
    - Folder #6, 1940 (Box Series V-1)
    - Folder #7, ca. 1944 (Box Series V-1)
    - Folder #8, 1946 (Box Series V-1)
      USC/LASL?
    - Folder #9, 1946-1948 (Box Series V-2)
    - Folder #10, 1947-1948 (Box Series V-2)
    - Folder #11, 1951 (Box Series V-2)
      Harvard seminar on problems
    - Folder #12, 1951-1983 (Box Series V-2)
      Harvard/LASL
    - Folder #13, 1966-1980 (Box Series V-2)
    - Folder #14, 1969-1970 (Box Series V-2)
      University of Colorado-problems and remarks in physics
    - Folder #15, 1977-1983 (Box Series V-2)
    - Folder #16, 1977-1983 (Box Series V-2)
      University of Florida
    - Folder #17, 1979-1981 (Box Series V-2)
    - Folder #18, 1981-1982 (Box Series V-2)
    - Folder #19, 1981-1983 (Box Series V-3)
    - Folder #20, 1982-1983 (Box Series V-3)
    - Folders #21-37, n.d. (Box Series V-3)
    - Folders #38, n.d. (Box Series V-3)
      3 incomplete notepads
  - Research notes (unbound) (Box Series V-4)
    - Folder#1, 1937-1963 (Box Series V-4)
      Misc.; some in Polish
    - Folder #2, 1973-1974 (Box Series V-4)
      See oversize Series V
    - Folder #3, 1977-1983 (Box Series V-4)
    - Folder #4, n.d. (Box Series V-4)
      Pattern recognition
      Schrandt, Robert G.
    - Folders #5-22, n.d. (Box Series V-4)
    - Folder #23, n.d. (Box Series V-4)
      All oversize
- Series VI. Calendars and address books, 1934-1984, 2.0 Linear feet 4 boxes
  Volumes that were maintained by Ulam, spanning a significant portion of his lifetime. Calendars are most valuable as detailed records of Ulam's daily appointments, correspondence, and may include short mathematical notes. They appear in a variety of formats, including pocket, desk, and wall calendars, with pocket calendars often divided into four volumes per year. Some calendars are incomplete, due to the fact that Ulam removed pages to write notes and reminders, and in many cases, entire volumes from a year of pocket calendars are missing. Twelve address books are filed at the end of the series and mainly contain entries for fellow mathematicians and scientists. All volumes are arranged chronologically when the date has been ascertained, the remainder are grouped at the end of the series.
  - Calendar (Box Series VI-1)
    - Folder #1, 1934-1935 (Box Series VI-1)
      From Harvard; some in Polish
    - Folder #2, 1942 (Box Series VI-1)
      From University of Wisconsin
    - Folder #3, 1945 (Box Series VI-1)
      From LASL
    - Folder #4, 1946 (Box Series VI-1)
      From USC and LASL
    - Folder #5, 1947 (Box Series VI-1)
    - Folder #6, 3 Jan.-19 Mar. 1947 (Box Series VI-1)
      Loose pages of desk calendar
    - Folder #7, 1947-1955 (Box Series VI-1)
      Incomplete; loose pages from LASL desk calendar
    - Folder #8, 1948 (Box Series VI-1)
      From LASL; in 4 parts
    - Folder #9, 1949 (Box Series VI-1)
      In 4 parts
    - Folder #10, 1950 (Box Series VI-1)
    - Folder #11, 1951 (Box Series VI-1)
      Incomplete in 3 of 4 parts
    - Folder #12, [1951,1952?] (Box Series VI-1)
    - Folder #13, 1952 (Box Series VI-1)
    - Folder #14, [1953-1956?] (Box Series VI-1)
    - Folder #15, 1954 (Box Series VI-1)
      Incomplete in 2 of 4 parts
    - Folder #16, 12 Jan.-6 Sept. 1956 (Box Series VI-2)
      Incomplete; loose pages of desk calendar
    - Folder #17, 1956 (Box Series VI-2)
      Incomplete in 1 of 4 parts
    - Folder #18, 10 June 1956-16 June 1957 (Box Series VI-2)
      From Harvard
    - Folder #19, 27 Aug. 1956-1 Sept. 1957 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #20, 31 July-31 1957 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #21, [1957?] (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #22, 3 Feb.-17 1958 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #23, 1958 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #24, 1959 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #25, 1 Feb.-7 Dec. 1960 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #26, [1960,1961?] (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #27, 3 Oct.-21 Nov. 1962 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #28, [1962?] (Box Series VI-2)
      In 2 parts
    - Folder #29, 7 June-14 Dec. 1963 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #30, 1964 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #31, [1964?] (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #32, 1964 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #33, 1965 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #34, 1966 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #35, 1966 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Folder #36, 1967 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #37, 1967 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #38, 1968 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #39, 1969 (Box Series VI-3)
      From University of Colorado; in 4 parts
    - Folder #40, 1970 (Box Series VI-3)
      From University of Colorado; incomplete in 3 of 4 parts
    - Folder #41, 1971 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #42, 1972 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #43, 1973 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #44, 1974 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #45, 1975 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #46, 1976 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #47, 1977 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #48, 1978 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #49, 1979 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #50, [1979?] (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #51, 1980 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #52, 1981 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Folder #53, 1982 (Box Series VI-4)
    - Folder #54, 1983 (Box Series VI-4)
    - Folder #55, 1984 (Box Series VI-4)
    - Folder #56, n.d. (Box Series VI-4)
      3 unidentified
  - Address books (Box Series VI-4)
    - Folder #1, 1941 (Box Series VI-4)
    - Folder #2, n.d. (Box Series VI-4)
      4 books
    - Folder #3, n.d. (Box Series VI-4)
      2 of 4 books from LASL
    - Folder #4, n.d. (Box Series VI-4)
      1 of 2 books from University of Colorado
    - Folder #5, n.d. (Box Series VI-4)
      photocopy
- Series VII. Talks and interviews, 1937-1984, 2.0 Linear feet 4 boxes